

Dear MD /Sir.

I wish to apply for a job of QC/QA / Inspector / Auditor in your company. I have been over 25 years working in the Garment/ Textile /Bags with same service for various items in company and several Rep. Offices as a Quality Controller. I have training course in Singapore 6 months about Quality Controller. I hope that my application will be received and I will have an opportunity for interview as your convenience.

Yours Respectfully.

CURRICULUM VITAE.

Full name : Le Khac Phi Hung.

Age : 44 years old. Date of birth : 08/04/1974.

Sex : Male. Marital status : Married.

Contact address: 44 Le Van Chi Str -Thu Duc dist. - Ho Chi Minh city-VIET NAM

Telephone : 0918380508.

Email :

: prestpoeric@yahoo.com

Skype: eric.le4

Currently salary: \$ USD 1300 /Month (Net salary)
Expect salary: \$ USD 1500/Month or Negotiable

Education:

Graduated from Ho Chi Minh City University Technology Education School.

Major : Textile/ Garment.

Language : English-

Profess : Quality Controller/ QA / Inspector / Auditor

Work experience:

1- From 1995 to 1998: I worked for Sai Gon 3 company as a Technician.

At here:

Just I am leaving out from high school so that I want study more experience of mine.

I make paper pattern and check T/P before going to production process).

Almost handle the quality during production processing.

Must be follow up and solve happen problems due to technical / workmanship / spec issue ...

Also some time may be to make the samples if necessary...

This time handle products in Local market.

2- From 1998 to 2002: I worked for TMI Singapore Vinh Hung Join venture company as a QA Manager(At here: I am responsible for all the goods Quality: checking the fabric, accessories, consumption, marker, cutting, sewing, packing, carton, inline and final inspection before to shipment.

I must be follow up and solve any quality happen problems during production / ironing / packing, inline and final audit.

I control all QC /QA staff in factory.

Arrange the quality systems to meet with Customer require.

Training for QC / QA full understand how to do inspect.

Regular opening meeting by QA dept.

Discuss with Merchandising dept. To workable together and others Dept

Report to Director directly if have big problems issue...

**As here I had been handled: Adidas, Nike and Fila brands, this is sport ware for woven and knit orders with items: Jacket, Pant, Short, Polo Shirt, T shirt, outerwear/

3- From 2002 to 2007: I am worked for ACTS Korea- Viet Nam Rep Office as a QC (At here: I should responsible for all the Quality issue. Every day I am going to factories to conduct inspection and checking/approval the PP samples before they start mass production .Follow- up the production status and conduct inline/final inspection before shipment.

I responsibility from A –Z the quality of goods.

Solve any quality issue at factories.

Also need to training for new QC staff

Report inspection report to head office in Korea every day.

Take care the production plan to keep delivery date.

**As here I had been handled :John Henry, PVH, Supreme, Yongo, Baw, Shopko and Chaps brands ,This is Fashion products for woven orders with items :Jacket, Shirt outerwear ,Pant ,Suit.

4- From 12-2007 to 12-2011 : I worked for : PRESTTIGE GLOBAL USA as Assistant QC Manager for " PRESTIGE co .,ltd in Taiwan office .

I handle all orders at Viet Nam.

Discuss QC work with Vendor /Factories.

Evaluate Factory audit & C –T–Pat.

Conduct inline and final inspection before shipment.

Training QC work for new QC.

Training /suggestion to Vendor / Factories full understand above the Quality standard of PRESTIGE issue.

Pilot PP meeting /Approval samples before production.

I know AQL level systems.

Report inspection report to Taiwan office after QC work finish at factories.

Solve any quality happen problems during conduct inspection.

Regular opening meeting with QC staff every week.

Follow up weekly report. / Production plan by supply / delivery shipment.,

Handle payment for QC work expenditure /salary in VIET NAM.

**As here I had been handled :FDS,D &G ,Hamrick ,Bon worth, Boscoss, Red, Beall Outlet ,Shopko brands ,This is Fashion products for knits orders with items :Jacket, outerwear ,Pant, sleepwear ,dress ,skirt .

Also I handled for Hard line: Backpack, Handbag, and Wallet ...

5-From 2012 to Jul-2015: I am working for 5.11 Tactical series as QA/Inspector in Viet Nam.

At here I handle conduct PPM, Inline and Final inspection for soft line and hard line, will send out the inspection report to HK office every day after finished work at factories. Further, follow up the Inspection Report Factory weekly to control and arrange according, to make the Factory Performance Report every end Month, etc.,,

**As here I had been handled :5.11 Tactical Series brands ,This is the Uniform products of FBI, Police, Emmy for Woven and knits orders with items :Jacket, Outerwear ,Pant, Shirt, Polo Shirt, T- shirt ,Short , underwear and Handbag, Backpack, Trolley, and all Pouches..

6- From Aug-2015 to 12-2016: I am working part time in SGS and Inspectorio

** At here AM conduct Dupro /inline /Final inspection at factories side for solfline

7-From 12-2016 to now: I am working at Linmark group HKO.

** As here my Main job is conduct PPM, Inline and final inspection, and follow up production in factory to match with Linmark standard,
Resolve any quality issue in factory, support other QA if need.

FOREIGN LANGUGES:

.English and Vietnamese.

OTHER SKILL:

Able to use the PC and related software including: MS word / MS excel. , MS power point / Mail $\,$, fax,

Interview for new QC experience.

Excellent in solving problems

Can sourcing for new Vendor / factory

Negotiation with factories about the costing /price.

PERSONAL CHARACTERS:

- -Very careful.
- -Hard working
- -May be working overtime if necessary.
- -Like working in an independent environment.
- -And able to work under pressure ...

INTERESTING:

- -Watch TV international program.
- -Go out with friendly /or my family on the weekend.

I look forward to hearing from your soon.

Thanks.

Best & Regards.

Le Khac Phi Hung. (Eric Le)